<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Natalia Díaz Rodríguez, PhD</title>
    <link>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Natalia Díaz Rodríguez, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>S-RL Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/s-rl-toolbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/s-rl-toolbox/</guid>
      <description> S-RL Toolbox: Reinforcement Learning (RL) and State Representation Learning (SRL) Toolbox for Robotics.
Github repository: https://github.com/araffin/robotics-rl-srl
Documentation: https://s-rl-toolbox.readthedocs.io
Paper: https://arxiv.org/abs/1809.09369
Associated Stable Baselines Medium post: https://towardsdatascience.com/stable-baselines-a-fork-of-openai-baselines-reinforcement-learning-made-easy-df87c4b2fc82?source=user_profile---------2------------------
Main Features  10 RL algorithms (Stable Baselines included) logging / plotting / visdom integration / replay trained agent hyperparameter search (hyperband, hyperopt) integration with State Representation Learning (SRL) methods (for feature extraction) visualisation tools (explore latent space, display action proba, live plot in the state space, &amp;hellip;) robotics environments to compare SRL methods easy install using anaconda env or Docker images (CPU/GPU)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continual AI</title>
      <link>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/continual-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/continual-ai/</guid>
      <description>Continual AI is an Open Community of Researchers and Enthusiasts on Continual/Lifelong Learning and AI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DREAM EU H2020 Project</title>
      <link>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nataliadiaz.github.io/project/dream/</guid>
      <description>DREAM is a robotic project that incorporates sleep and dream-like processes within cognitive architecture. This enables an individual robot or groups of robots to consolidate their experience into more useful and generic formats, thus improving their future ability to learn and adapt. DREAM relies on Evolutionary Neurodynamic ensemble methods as a unifying principle for discovery, optimization, re-structuring and consolidation of knowledge. This new paradigm will make the robot more autonomous in its acquisition, organization and use of knowledge and skills just as long as they comply with the satisfaction of pre-established basic motivations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>